I've already found
the woman you wanted me to look for.
The woman named Joycelyn Trinidad.
She's been a domestic helper in France
for 30 years.
Is she the one you're looking for?
No.
Maybe it's a blessing in disguise
if you lose your project in Blacksmith.
Isn't that Savana?
- Have you watched her video?
- Yes.
She said a lot about her mother.
Let's go somewhere else?
Sorry.
Where are we going?
Looks like we're going on vacation.
It's just me.
I'm used to traveling alone on my birthday.
Is it because
I was busy with work in Casa Fuerte?
If I say you'll return to Casa Fuerte,
you'll do as I say!
Do you understand?
Why does Uncle Ramon talk
as if he has more authority than dad?
Have you forgotten about it?
We take care of his businesses.
You can go against anyone
except Congressman Ramon.
If you do, you'll get what you deserve.
Let's go, girls.
This. Let's try this.
- I think this is better.
- Is that for me?
Perfect timing.
I think I need a massage.
You wish.
You don't need a massage.
Your bones need some twisting.
You're so mean.
You haven't changed a bit.
You're still as violent.
It's because of you.
And what's stressing you out?
You get everything you want.
Your son and I are the same.
We're both stubborn.
Let me make this clear.
Liam is happy with the film
he's making right now.
If you can't support him,
just leave my son alone.
Tess...
Your son loves you so much.
He will do everything for you.
I'll just get this.
This is for what she got.
Didn't you get anything?
You said it wouldn't work for me.
[Records Section]
Sir, here are Mrs. Teresita Buenaventura's
records.
Thank you so much. Thank you.
Please sign here.
Sure.
- Over here?
- Yeah.
- Thank you.
Ten million pesos?
I paid this much money?
How much do I make in Casa Fuerte?
And what exactly is the job
that I do for dad and Congressman Ramon?
I'm sorry, the subscriber cannot be reached.
Please try again later.
I'm sorry, the sub...
[Call Ended]
[Compose Message]
[To: Via]
[Via, I just wanted to ask you something]
[about my working relationship
with your dad.]
[I will go see you at your office.]
Great job today.
Please include this one, too.
Yeah, yeah. Bring it to the car.
I want to thank you, Via.
What for?
For defending you?
Or for the villains' wardrobe malfunction?
Both.
It's nothing.
I'm your friend.
Thank you...
Because...
I can feel...
and see that you treat me as a friend.
It's hard to find honest people in showbiz.
Trust me, I know.
Because I know... I can trust you.
I'll be shameless this time, Via.
Can I...
Can I ask you a favor?
I'll be shameless this time, Via.
Can I...
Can I ask you a favor?
Of course.
What can I do for you?
I want to have an interview in your magazine.
Interview?
About what?
Let's just say that...
I want to clear the issues against me.
My mom, who's a terror manager,
is so controlling.
I'm like a goldfish placed in a tiny tank.
Why can't she just flush me in the toilet?
And you want to make decisions
for your life and career?
If I let you decide for yourself,
you would have lost your career already.
You would have been pregnant.
I should be the one to apologize.
This has become our normal setup.
You have to sneak just to see me.
Maybe this is the sacrifice we have to make.
If only I was a father
that you could introduce to people...
Someone you could be proud of...
Then you won't have a hard time.
You know what?
The photo shoot for our new campaign
is ongoing right now.
We're calling it "Bare Naked",
because the theme of the whole thing
is laying bare and stripping down.
You know what I mean, like...
No masks, no walls, just laying it all bare.
Perfect.
Are you ready to reveal everything?
Yes...
I'm ready.
After that, let's take closer shots, okay?
Beautiful, I love it.
I really like the eye makeup.
More, more!
Closer, please.
Later. There, there. That's nice.
- There.
- That's nice.
Beautiful!
Love!
What are you doing here?
I sent you a message,
but I don't think you've read it.
Really? I'm so sorry.
We're so busy.
Look. Savana's photo shoot is still ongoing.
Yeah.
This is the first time I'm going to say this.
I want to start by telling you
who I really am.
The person you know...
Savana...
She's not who I really am.
My real name is...
Joycelyn Trinidad.
I want...
I want everyone to know me...
as Joyce.
The real me.
Joyce...
I realized...
I realized that if I really
wanted to be a role model,
I shouldn't be ashamed of who I really am.
And I won't be ashamed of where I came from.
I was so drunk last night.
Did I say something inappropriate?
- Love?
- Joyce.
Joyce?
Joyce... Joycelyn Trinidad.
Who is she?
Excuse me. I'm sorry.
Let's take a break.
Via!
Miss Via?
Are you okay?
Miss Via, is it just a coincidence...
or is Savana the Joycelyn Trinidad
you asked me to find?
Love?
Can you give us privacy first?
I'll just give Savana a sponge bath.
Via, what are you doing here?
Surprise!
I just thought I'd surprise you.
I said leave!
I'm not leaving because I love you!
I think that's her.
Why do you want me to find her?
Queenie, get out.
Get out.
- Sorry.
- You don't have to know that.
- Out.
Joyce.
Joyce...
Sir, everything's good now.
Miss Savana, excuse me.
Thank you.
Are you worried yet?
About what?
Our film's billing.
The posters will no longer
bear the name "Savana".
It will be...
"Joycelyn".
Well, that's the least of my concerns.
Your boyfriend told me
to take care of you, remember?
Suitor.
Hans and I are not together yet.
I'm still trying to see
how patient he is in courting me.
He might get tired.
I hope he can wait.
Wait?
Wait until I'm ready to make
big decisions for myself.
Well, I guess this is a good start.
I mean, telling everyone
your real name, Joyce.
Yes.
Although I can retain
my screen name, Savana...
I like Joyce better.
I'm also happy that you've shown courage.
I mean, the bashers can no longer use
your too-good-to-be-true image against you.
Believe it or not,
I know how it feels to bottle up
everything inside.
Maybe you need to do an interview with Via.
Maybe you're right.
Why, Liam?
Do you also have something to confess?
Via.
I'll let you know
once the magazine publishes
your shoot and interview, Savana.
I mean...
Joyce.
Via, thank you so much.
You said you have something to tell me.
Yes, Via.
There's something I need to tell you.
So, Savana...
Joyce.
I'll go ahead, Joyce.
Via...
About my...
question...
This is about my working relationship
with your dad.
Because of everything
that has happened lately,
I'm just worried that
I might not be able to fulfill
some of my obligations to him.
You know that as much as possible,
I don't meddle with my dad's businesses.
Because?
Because he doesn't like it.
That's one thing you both agree on, right?
You don't want anyone
interfering with your life.
Do we have a problem, Via?
You tell me...
Love.
Is there something I need to worry about?
Mommy?
Sweetie...
I hope you understand...
that everything I do is for you.
Yes, Mommy.
I don't forget that.
I want to tell you something.
I don't want to hear it
if it's not good news.
What is it? New project?
New endorsement? Or an award?
Mommy, I just want to tell you...
I just want to tell you
that I love you so much.
And I will never intend...
to hurt you or make you suffer.
I thought you were going
to say something else.
Good night, Mommy.
Okay, good night.
Maybe you're tired.
Maybe this is not the right time to ask.
I'll just ask you next time.
Wait, Love.
Sorry. Sorry.
I just have a lot on my mind.
I'm sorry.
Okay, what do you want to talk about?
It's okay, it's okay.
I'm sorry for bothering you.
Maybe I should just drive you home.
[Girl with Periwinkle Hair]
Hello, friends!
It's me again,
your trusted showbiz authority,
the Girl with the Periwinkle Hair!
Well, it takes a great actress
to portray challenging roles.
But a great level of acting is needed
to pretend to be someone you're not.
Well, I'm talking about this famous actress
who just revealed her true identity.
Apparently, the image she has
all these years,
like the roles she took, is fake.
Fictional, made-up, manufactured!
The actress I'm talking about
is none other than,
your favorite and most in-demand, Savana.
She's introducing herself now
as Joycelyn Trinidad.
And according to my sources,
she hid her true identity
because of a deep, dark secret
involving her past and her family.
Her father is drug-dependent
who even went to jail
because of a drug-related crime.
Oh, poor Savana.
Or should I say...
- This is why I prefer independent films.
- poor Joyce...
Come on, Leroy!
Can't you give Savana a little sympathy?
I feel bad for her.
I know how it feels when
the whole world against you.
It reminds me of my husband's family.
Calm down, Miss Megan.
You look so affected.
Or maybe the real victim here is her father.
Boss Bro?
Have you seen the latest video about Savana
by the Girl with Periwinkle Hair?
I'm watching it now, Borj.
Bye.
What kind of a daughter
can forsake her own father
for fame and money?
Joyce...
Who in the world is behind that?
I didn't know Savana's real name is Joycelyn.
Why does Joycelyn seem familiar to me?
Joyce?
Joyce...
Maybe that's how it really is
when you turn yourself into a commodity.
So friends, be careful who you look up to.
Bye for now.
This is your trusted showbiz authority,
the Girl with the Periwinkle Hair!
Bye!
Savana!
Savana, what did you do?
What did you do?
Who did you tell about your real name?
Who?
I... I only told one person, Mommy.
Come on, Savana!
Where's your boss?
- Miss Via is in an important meeting.
- Excuse me.
Can we talk?
Girls.
- Savana, what are you doing?
- Don't deny it, Via.
I thought we were friends.
But what did you do?
I don't know what you're talking about.
Please, just admit it!
Admit what?
What is going on?
Get back to work. Back to work. Go!
How convenient is it
that after I told you about my real name,
the Girl with Periwinkle Hair came out
with a video about me
and even dragged my father into it!
My whole life is now out in the open!
Wait, what? I'm sorry...
Via, I just realized...
You only defended me from Maxine
so I would trust you.
You really think
I'm behind that malicious content?
[I Am Joyce]
Savana...
or should I call you Joyce?
I admired what you did.
I even told my team
to rush and include this article
in our latest issue.
I didn't sleep just to write it.
And I swear I really did my best
to write it as fair as I can.
It's beyond my control, Savana.
I have no control over people's minds
if they will put malice
to what you confessed, okay?
I don't get you.
What are you talking about now?
Via, I... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I thought...
I thought you were the only one
who knew about it.
I didn't know
that you already published the article.
I'm sorry, Via.
I just can't bear all the bashing.
Just take it.
Sorry, Joyce, just... get out of my office.
Just go.
Hello, Dad?
Okay, Dad. I'm on my way there.
Liam?
Because of the new issue about Savana,
or should I call her Joyce...
We decided to pull her out of Josh's movie.
Wait, why?
Do we already know the truth?
What do you mean by truth?
Liam, in this industry,
nothing is more important than
people's perceptions.
Savana is so ruined
because a lot of people
are malicious and gullible like you.
What did you say?
Stop, you two!
Liam, you can defend Savana or Joyce
all you want.
But this issue regarding her
ex-con and drug-dependent father,
and the fact that Savana hid it
because she's ashamed of him?
This will cause serious damage
to the film she's doing with Josh.
Sorry, Liam.
I want to win the elections.
I don't want any more trouble.
I want you to release my movie
before the campaign period,
which is a couple of months from now.
Don't we care about anything
but our own agenda?
You should pity Joyce.
Everyone's critical of her,
and now you're letting her down?
You can laugh at our reason.
But I'm not going to produce a film
with a problematic actress.
Josh's role is a public servant.
You don't expect him to have
a rebellious leading lady?
Is that really the reason?
Uncle Ramon, can you say something?
You did tell me something, remember?
Liam...
Watch your mouth, Liam.
Why don't you just tell the truth?
Joyce is getting caught in between,
and my film is delayed
because you have a problem with me.
The truth is, you want me out of this project
so I can go back and work for you.
I know how much I owe Casa Fuerte.
And you're making me pay it back
by making me do things.
Well, let's do this.
You can pull me out of this project,
but you must retain Joyce.
Liam, will you shut up?
All right.
You said it yourself.
Joyce, A.K.A. Savana,
will stay in this project
if you return to Casa Fuerte.
My friend.
I apologize for what my son did.
Mr. Trinidad, we only want to hear your side.
Does Edmond Trinidad live here?
Savana's father? Yes, he lives here.
Mr. Trinidad, we only want to make it clear.
Savana, I mean, Joyce,
is now in the hot seat.
Did she hide her real identity
because she's ashamed of you?
She's a bad woman!
Savana's here!
Her name's Joyce!
She's here. Take a video.
Leave her alone!
Leeches!
Please stop.
That's enough. Talk to me.
Mr. Trinidad, just give us something.
Is it true, Savana,
that you changed your name?
I thought about it carefully before I did it.
When I confess my real name,
I know a lot will be revealed about my life.
And I accept all that.
I accept that a lot of you
will be disappointed.
I accept that a lot will turn their backs.
But I'm begging you. Talk to me instead.
Keep my loved ones out of it.
Especially my father,
because I love him so much.
My dad and I are doing fine.
I'm begging you,
don't drag my family into this.
I can afford to lose everything
except my loved ones.
- Oh, come on.
- That's just drama.
She's just being defensive.
- Should we believe that?
- Is it true?
- Do you believe it?
- We won't believe it!
Mr. Trinidad, please give a short statement.
Get out of my property!
- Mommy!
- Get out of here! The show is over!
It's over! Get lost!
- Joanne.
- Get lost!
Get out of here!
Sorry, Auntie.
- Mom?
- It's okay.
Son? We're here in the kitchen.
Via?
What happened?
Savana fought with Via.
Savana barged into her office
and accused her that she is the Girl with...
What's the color of her hair again?
Violet, purple...
Periwinkle!
That's it.
It was...
It was because of my interview with her.
She told me her real name, remember?
It was so easy for her to assume
that I was the one who revealed
the issue of her family.
I didn't do anything like that.
She said I'm the online bully
who does nothing good in life.
Via...
Via, I'm sorry if you got offended, but...
But what?
But maybe you should try...
putting yourself in her shoes.
I mean...
I know what she did was wrong.
But because of what she's going through...
maybe we should understand
why she's careless.
Excuse me.
- Auntie, thank you.
- Dear...
- Thank you.
- Via, my dear.
Via, wait.
Sorry, Liam.
I didn't know that problems
have a hierarchy...
That Joyce is going through something worse,
than what she did to me?
My gosh.
Sorry for coming here.
I thought you would be on my side.
Mom...
Was I wrong?
Liam, it's not about being right or wrong.
Via is your girlfriend.
Liam, dear, listen to me.
This is the only time I will talk about this.
Son...
You know about everything I had been through
because of your dad.
You know every pain I went through
because he couldn't stand by me.
Liam, son, don't be like Danilo.
Don't treat Via like how your dad treated me.
Now, if there's someone that matters
more to you, Liam.
Son...
Man up.
Admit the truth...
to yourself...
and to the person you can possibly hurt.
My dear,
please find out which network
sent those reporters to Edmond's house.
Get me an appointment with them, please?
Okay, bye.
Dear, don't take this the wrong way.
But you need to listen to your mom.
I'm glad...
that you were able to tell the world
who you really are.
Your real name, the life you had...
But it's true that...
I'm the one who did wrong.
And I can't bear it, Joyce...
if you and your mom will lose
everything you worked hard for.
Just because of me.
Dad...
Listen to your mom.
She won't do anything that can harm you.
And...
don't worry about me.
I can handle this.
Joyce...
I'm at this point in my life again...
that I have to make a big decision.
They want me back in Casa Fuerte...
Back to the life I thought I wanted.
You know what, Joyce?
Only one thing is clear.
That I should not do what I did
with the typewriter.
I shouldn't be selfish.
Joyce, you should...
finish your dream project.
Maybe...
this is only right.
Because other people are getting hurt, too.
So even though I was so...
I was so happy...
to be with you again...
Even though I thought...
we could fulfill our dreams together.
Even if it's hard...
Who said it was easy?
You're already making it a habit.
You only come to me when you have a problem.
I don't come here to see you.
Her.
Would you rather talk to her than me?
Bro, life is an endless cycle
of making choices.
Like the junk I scavenged.
Most of them are useless.
But it will surprise you...
because they can still be used.
See?
What if I tell you that...
this is not the life I chose?
What do you mean you didn't choose this?
Come on, bro.
That is what's wrong in our society.
People suffer...
because decisions are made by people
who won't own up to their mistakes.
Bro...
People need to learn how to
take responsibility for their decisions.
I regret a lot of the decisions I made.
That's why I have this kind of life.
But I'm already here. What else can I do?
That's why I deal with it.
I endure it.
I stand by it.
Because I can't blame anyone but myself.
What was the wrong decision you made?
That's the problem. I can't remember anymore.
But, bro, the important question is...
How about you?
What mistake you made should you face?
Stefano Lualhati is his real name.
He was from Verde Village.
Verde Village?
Why, Liam? Do you know the kid's parents?
Liam, regarding Savana's action scenes.
I hope you take care of her.
I mean, Joyce.
Sorry, I'm not used to calling you Joyce.
Liam is so used to calling her Joyce.
- Actually, Via...
- Can I talk to you?
Hans, just so you know,
Liam is not working at Blacksmith anymore.
He'll return to Casa Fuerte.
What about our movie?
We have established by now
that my boyfriend has a lot of secrets.
Is Via still mad at me?
I'm sorry.
So she's still mad at me.
Don't blame yourself.
I don't have anyone else to blame but me.
I think that is what you should do too.
Take full accountability
for all your decisions.
I want to apologize to you.
I know I did wrong.
I told Liam
that I was not ready yet to see you.